STUDENT AT FIB - UPC OF BACHELOR DEGREE IN INFORMATICS ENGINEERING MAJOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Carrer Sepúlveda 110, Barcelona

□ (+34) 601054286 | wsanchez.gassull@gmail.com | osanchyy | osanchyy

About Me.

I was born on December 15, 1998 in Barcelona. I am a 21 year old student, currently I'm studying Computer Engineering, with major in IT at FIB - UPC. I have worked for 14 months in inLab FIB.

I am a fast learner and good problem solver. I consider myself an algorithm enthusiast,I like learning new thinks and taking new challenges. Also I like to have responsibilities and lead tasks.

Education

UPC (Universitat Politécnica de Catalunya) - FIB

Barcelona

BACHELOR DEGREE IN INFORMATICS ENGINEERING

Sept. 2016 - Present

Specialized in computer science and IT

Cybersecurity course

Barcelona

JEDI UPC courses 2019 February 2019

Deep Learning course

Barcelona

JEDI UPC courses 2019

June 2019

Work Experience

InLab FIB Barcelona

PYTHON DEVELOPER INTERN Sept 2018 - Sept 2020

- · Virtual Mobility Lab project: Barcelona traffic simulator
- Controvèrsies: Online tool for UOC's page
- Car sharing: Optimization problem oriented on locations.
- collab: Online tool for evaluating thesis online

JEDI Estudiants d'Informàtica

Barcelona

Developer Aug 2017 - Sept 2018

- Developing different types of projects using the best case technologies.
- Use of Agile methods such as Scrum

Extracurricular Activity_

The Game Barcelona

HACKUPC 2019 - Present

HackUPC is the student hackathon from the Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya. I am in the organizer team and I've been working in the TheGame department on this edition. In this team, we are charged of building the CTF platform, thinking and building every exercise/problem.

Web Dev Barcelona

HACKUPC 2019 - Present

In this team, we have to build all the tech infrastructure the hackathon will need, build internal tools such as check-in app, hardware lab app, etc.

Skills_

PROGRAMING LANGUAGES

Comfortable: Javascript, C++, Python, Go, bash

Familiar: x86, Java, C, Rust



Catalan: Native/BilingualLevel CSpanish: Native/BilingualLevel CEnglish: IntermediateLevel B2

Italian: Basic

Others____

HACKATONS

Nov 2017	Lauzhack: 24 hours hackaton - we developed a Website called Drink me	Switzerland
Nov 2017	HackEPS: 24 hours hackaton - We participated to a CTF - Algorithm game	Lleida
Mar 2018	HackMobility: 24 hours hackaton - we developed a web helper called EzBicing and we won the	Barcelona
	ThinkBig - Telefónica challenge.	
Nov. 2018	HackEPS: 24 hours hackaton - We participated to a CTF - Algorithm game and we won	Lleida
Nov 2018	Lauzhack: 24 hours hackaton - we developed a Website game controlled by pitch of your voice,	Switzerland
	called BirdPitch	
April 2019	Copenhacks: 24 hours hackaton - we built a full platform with hardware, frontend and backend	Copenaghen
	that lets you control your time, called <i>TimeCube</i>	
Nov 2019	Lauzhack: 24 hours hackaton - We developed a website that lets a professor control their class and	Switzerland
	if there are any bullied or students alone, called it ClassControl	